e-2
It appears to be a ticket for a nearby relaxation spot. According to the ticket, it had lots of beautiful flora in its gardens.

While many of my creators were content with modifying species to suit their needs, some fervently believed that natural life was sacred.<LINE>Their beliefs were a rather small minority, and I doubt they approved of my creation.

Tickets like this one would have been very expensive back then, although I doubt this data pearl has value to any creature presently.<LINE>Aside from those curious scavengers that is.