0-46
I'm sorry little creature, for this is not a pearl.<LINE>Well, it could be considered a pearl, but not the contemporary kind.

This object is a polished stone orb. Its surface is currently blank,<LINE>but in ancient times it would have been covered in small engravings.

It is a highly inefficient form of information storage, but I can't deny how important it might have been in the past.<LINE>After all, the pearls scattered across the world today all hearken back "proto-pearls" like this.

Even though this orb has been made illegible with time, it’s incredible that such an ancient artifact<LINE>has lasted so long in the first place. What a remarkable find you’ve made, little creature!