0-46
The pearl contains an excerpt from an old and longstanding argument concerning the preservation of a religious site.<LINE>The author of the pearl was pushing to remove restrictions put on the site's accessibility, while the opposition aimed to keep them firmly in place.

I find the whole argument rather daft, if not downright hypocritical.<LINE>My structure is the ultimate testament to what little regard they had for their "sacred" sites.

Of course, I don’t take any particular interest in these ancient monuments.<LINE>If you search deep enough, you will find that the ground is littered with temples all over the place.

Had you not initially arrived here with such an imperative item, I would have guided you away to the temple grounds just west of here.<LINE>I could still direct you to that place, but you seem preoccupied with other struggles.