0-46
It’s an old letter concerning an old site simply referred to as the temple grounds.<LINE>It was written around the time of the first generation of iterators, so some of the details are familiar to me.

The temple grounds were a rather notable religious landmark. Up until the discovery of underground ruins during the<LINE>construction of the void fluid filtration systems, the site was considered the oldest ancient settlement in the world.

At some point in time, regulations were put in place that barred access to the ruins, as the site was deemed, “too sacred to risk defacement.”<LINE>This letter specifically asked for these laws to be repealed, as the increasing rainfall meant that the window of opportunity to utilize these ruins was closing.

Stubborn to their old ways, the higher members of the court declined the request, leaving any potential secrets the site had undiscovered.

I suppose now that the ancients are long gone, you are free to explore as much of the ruins as you’d like.<LINE>Not that the old laws meant anything to a creature like you.