0-1
A register listing the residents of an old spiritual facility, dating shortly before the mass evacuation effort to us iterator.
These people hated us, and I suppose not without reason, we made their holy spaces uninhabitable and forced them to live in newly constructed, entirely artificial living blocks.
Us Iterators didn't have a say in the matter either, we never do, but we were the target of their scorn and attempts at revenge more often than not.
And now they are gone, they were one of the first to take the void route once it precented itself on a mass scale.
What is the lesson in all this? You tell me.