0-1
This is a register listing the residents of an old spiritual facility, dating shortly before the mass evacuation effort<LINE>to the iterator cities. No doubt that those named here went up along with the others... Likely with much reluctance.

The contents aren't particularly interesting, just an index of names and their designated roles.

However, the temple itself was one with significant reputation, even during my time;<LINE>a resting grounds of sorts for those close to ascension, carved in a valley deep into the ground.

The site was constructed shortly after the discovery of the void sea, in the belief<LINE>that residing so close to it would bestow some kind of insight on the process of ascension.<LINE>A great deal of information on void fluid and spiritual practices relating to it was archived there.

Very few were given the honor of entering the grounds - only those close enough to enlightenment were considered worthy<LINE>of stepping on such holy soil, enriched by the void itself. There, they would make their final preparations before ascension.

Despite the state I am in now, I still remember how many memories and qualia donated to me came from that place.

I hope what little information remains in my memory banks now has satisfied you, little creature.
